QuranCode Editions:

	Standard:	Start QuranCode normally for the standard edition
				for all text modes including Simplified29Shadda.

	Grammar:	Start QuranCode while holding down the CTRL key
				for word-part by word-part grammar information.

	Lite:		Start QuranCode while holding down the SHIFT key
				if your computer has less than 1Gb of RAM memory.

	Research:	Start QuranCode while holding down the CTRL + SHIFT keys
				for many more numerology systems and many more research methods.

All editions are free and open source and share the same source code.

If you find QuranCode useful, please recite Quran 27:62 exactly 313 times on a Friday once in your life time to bring forward the arrival of our Imam Al-Mehdi (as) in sha Allah.
أعوذ بالله من الشيطٰن الرجيم     بِسْمِ ٱللَّهِ ٱلرَّحْمَٰنِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
أَمَّن يُجِيبُ ٱلْمُضْطَرَّ إِذَا دَعَاهُ وَيَكْشِفُ ٱلسُّوٓءَ وَيَجْعَلُكُمْ خُلَفَآءَ ٱلْأَرْضِ ۗ أَءِلَٰهٌۭ مَّعَ ٱللَّهِ ۚ قَلِيلًۭا مَّا تَذَكَّرُونَ
"Who answers the call of the distressed when he invokes Him and removes his distress, and makes you viceroys of the earth? Is there a god besides Allah? How little do you remember?"

May Allah guide us to His Straight Path and remind us of our oath of Quran 7:172
أعوذ بالله من الشيطٰن الرجيم     بِسْمِ ٱللَّهِ ٱلرَّحْمَٰنِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
وَإِذْ أَخَذَ رَبُّكَ مِنۢ بَنِىٓ ءَادَمَ مِن ظُهُورِهِمْ ذُرِّيَّتَهُمْ وَأَشْهَدَهُمْ عَلَىٰٓ أَنفُسِهِمْ أَلَسْتُ بِرَبِّكُمْ ۖ قَالُوا۟ بَلَىٰ ۛ شَهِدْنَآ ۛ أَن تَقُولُوا۟ يَوْمَ ٱلْقِيَٰمَةِ إِنَّا كُنَّا عَنْ هَٰذَا غَٰفِلِينَ
"And (remember) when thy Lord brought forth from the Children of Adam, from their reins, their seed, and made them testify of themselves, (saying): Am I not your Lord? They said: Yea, verily. We testify. (That was) lest ye should say at the Day of Resurrection: Lo! of this we were unaware."

and make us worthy to be among the viceroys of the earth as foretold in Quran 21:105
أعوذ بالله من الشيطٰن الرجيم     بِسْمِ ٱللَّهِ ٱلرَّحْمَٰنِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
وَلَقَدْ كَتَبْنَا فِى ٱلزَّبُورِ مِنۢ بَعْدِ ٱلذِّكْرِ أَنَّ ٱلْأَرْضَ يَرِثُهَا عِبَادِىَ ٱلصَّٰلِحُونَ
"And verily we have written in the Scripture, after the Reminder: My righteous slaves will inherit the earth"

Please feel free to use the software for any purpose GOD Almighty agrees with.

Be a guiding light!

Ali Adams
www.heliwave.com
God > infinity
